(Who's Going to Win?)
- Nice to see you. - Nice to see you.
By the way, you got injured...
- while running. - Yes.
- That happened last week. - You were quite fast.
Ready...
(Hyun Moo and Sung Hwan had a race in the middle of the night.)
(Moosain Bolt won the race.)
(And after a cutthroat match, )
(the two runners ended up with injuries.)
It bled a lot that day.
How could you get an injury...
- only after a short race? - Well,
- it shows you did your best. - Right.
- You didn't go easy on him. - As if his life depended on it.
I hope this will give us a chance to hold a sports day.
With these jokers?
Hyun Moo is a fast runner.
Let's do it once the weather gets better in fall.
I need to dominate CODE KUNST with my soccer skills too.
- Right. - CODE KUNST?
- I'll show you how I get past him. - I can beat you...
even in high heels.
- High heels? - I'll wear higher heels than you.
(Sure. We couldn't care less who wins.)
My gosh.
(Break Ground with the First Shovel at Last)
(Hyun Moo is sleeping soundly.)
(Squirming)
(Turning)
(He lets out a big yawn.)
(He gets up.)
Is it because you have a lot of machines at home?
It looks like a VIP room at a hospital.
- Doesn't it? - What are you wearing?
- His pajamas look like pillows. - His clothes too.
- What kind of pajamas are they? - Is that...
- part of the blanket? - A VIP patient.
It looks like it's a set with a diaper.
It looks like you're only wearing a diaper like the Boss Baby.
- I look so cute. - Right.
(Laughing)
(Baby Moomoo wakes up with fatigue.)
(Humming)
- What? - What's that?
Seriously?
There's always something new in his house.
(A strange object is placed in a corner of his bedroom.)
- What's that? - It happens every time. Seriously.
Is that a studio set or something?
(Is that not a real house?)
- Do you live in a cafe? - How could you say that?
There's always something new in your house.
It's been a while since my house was on TV.
Seriously. This is too much.
- It's driving me crazy. - Yes.
You see this in corporate buildings.
- Right. - In their lobbies and stuff.
Yes, you see in lobbies.
- And it spurts out water. - You know what?
You see that kind of wall at dermatology clinics too.
- Right. - Hospitals and subway stations too.
- Or at cafes. - Yes.
You also see it in a subway station.
Then do you live in a subway station?
I don't live in a subway station.
- What... - But...
I dreamed of doing this.
Designing an entire wall of my bedroom with plants.
I knew you and I would see eye to eye on this, Dae Ja Yeon.
(She's indeed Dae Ja Yeon.)
I'm crazy about greens and plants.
I did all sorts of things to my house.
I tried to grow plants, but I ended up killing them all.
I tried everything a long time ago.
I had plants that supposedly never died, but I killed them.
- You don't mix well with plants. - How beautiful.
- My plants in a three-tier cart... - I remember that.
- also died. - All of them died too.
People rarely kill those plants.
All of them died.
I thought I would never be able to grow plants.
But there's an agency that takes care of plants on my behalf.
I can just pay a monthly fee.
They regularly come to my house, trim my plants,
and change the water.
My plants are still alive thanks to the agency's help.
- He sounds like a rich Indian man. - He outsources it.
Of course, I have a desire to grow plants.
But my throat is never in good condition.
So keeping it hydrated is very important.
I hear a natural humidifier...
is more helpful than a machine.
I'm growing NASA-approved plants...
- that are known to purify air. - Come on.
(He breathes in nature as soon as he wakes up.)
- Anyway, the leaves are beautiful. - Right.
- It's a type of philodendron. - I hear...
- there are snakes too. - Right, that's the one.
- Phil-something. - Right.
That's beautiful, isn't it?
(He feels the leaves with love although he doesn't know its name.)
(He breathes in deeply through his nose.)
But they don't have a special scent.
Right. I bet it doesn't smell like anything.
- He's blowing his nose. - Yes.
(I'm not blowing my nose. I just love my plants.)
I'm crazy about plants.
(I love plants so much.)
They're going strong.
(Humming)
That...
- There's another one? - My gosh.
(I have one in my living room too.)
- Wait. - Why...
Did the plants go through the floor...
and spread on the wall in the living room?
What?
You don't know how much I adore them. What?
- It's funny because it's too much. - This is too much.
- Why is this too much? - Are there more plants...
- inside your fridge? - No.
Let me be honest now. You know what this looks like to me?
You look like a guy who's living in the bunker after the apocalypse.
Seriously. It does look like a scene from "2001: A Space Odyssey."
(It was released in 1968.)
- Seriously. - Mankind after 1,000 years...
- It's like an old sci-fi movie. - Like this.
- I bet he's like 300 years old. - Right.
Gosh, why is this so funny?
(He can't stop touching them as he deeply cares for them.)
Do you know how to prune them?
- Some of them dried up. - I see.
They need to go.
Is it funny because of his pajamas? Why is this so funny?
Doesn't he look like he's part of a new mankind?
- He looks like a different species. - Yes.
Right.
(Moomoo of the different species continues to stay busy.)
(He gets the juicer ready.)
(Opening)
That looks good.
- The bag comes with celery... - Celery.
- and apples. - I see.
They're very healthy.
(He washes the vegetables from the bag...)
(and adds them to the juicer.)
I can't believe this is my breakfast.
(He starts his breakfast with vegetables and fruits.)
Your diet has gotten so healthy.
(Pressing down)
(It starts operating.)
Extract.
- When it starts extracting... - That's fascinating.
Watch.
(It gives me tasty juice.)
- It's extracting the juice, right? - It is.
You don't have to remove the seeds. It only gives you the extract.
I only get the extract, and the solids come out separately.
I must drink up the last drop too.
Come on out.
This is so convenient.
(He has a sip of the juice that has greens he likes.)
(Hitting the spot)
I can drink the extract of vegetables and fruits together.
The latest trend is enzyme juice.
Really? What's that?
- It's enzyme-rich juice. - Enzyme?
I'm leading that trend now.
That hits the spot. My gosh.
(That was great juice.)
I should get changed now.
I'm going to be busy today.
(Hyun Moo comes out after getting changed.)
- The previous outfit was funny. - Right.
- He should've worn it outside. - You should've kept it on.
(Disappointed)
People will report me, thinking I'm a lunatic.
(People will report me.)
(He sets out in an outfit he won't get reported in.)
It's raining.
(The road is wet from the rain.)
(Don't you try me, I want some more)
Are you reciting the Buddhist chant?
(The Buddhist rapping resonates through the humidity.)
(He heads somewhere while humming endlessly.)
I can never copy her rap.
- Gimpo? - The airport?
- Hey, Hyun Moo. - Can you talk now?
Sure. I can talk. Go ahead.
I'm heading to Gimpo now.
- Really? - Are you in Gimpo now?
Yes, I am.
(By 100 of KOYOTE, a resident of Gimpo)
- My gosh. - It's By 100.
(The main rapper of KOYOTE, an influential group of his day)
(And he enjoys a healthy lifestyle in his neighborhood.)
- Right? - Yes.
I didn't know he lived in Gimpo.
He's been living there for a long time.
Remember what I told you the other day?
That I was looking into a house in Gimpo.
- What? - Yes.
Are you going to move?
I'm thinking about moving. I'm entertaining the idea.
I've been looking into some houses for 2 to 3 months.
- A house there? - Yes.
But don't you have more things to do around Gangnam?
When I thought about it, I rarely did things in Gangnam.
I have to come to Sangam or Yeouido for work.
You come to Sangam often. So Gimpo makes sense.
- Yes. - Right.
Here's the kind of house I want.
- Okay. - A house with...
my own private garden.
A house with a small yard. You know what I mean?
It doesn't need to be big.
I've been interested in a house in the suburbs for a while now.
In the entertainment industry,
I meet a lot of celebrities who live in a suburban home.
I'm so envious of them...
because I lived my entire life in apartments.
I want to grow my own vegetables like Na Rae.
I really want to try it.
A vegetable garden?
You're busy, but you manage.
Even Kian84 has some outdoor space on the rooftop.
(Kian84 also has a rooftop.)
- Why did they use that clip? - The rooftop.
I want a place where I can end my day...
while watching the sunset...
and enjoying the soft breeze.
When I stayed in the hanok a few years ago,
I woke up to the chirping of the birds.
- I still remember that. - Right. You loved that experience.
Gosh, who is that?
(His memory in the outdoor space is unforgettable.)
I think I like looking at greens.
(He enjoys looking at greens, )
(eating the greens, )
(and growing the greens.)
I prefer mountains to the sea.
(I prefer mountains to the sea.)
When I look at greenery, it truly relaxes me.
I want to live close to nature.
You know what? My mother...
- Yes. - lives in Gangseo-gu.
- My house is in Samseong-dong. - Yes.
We live so far from each other.
- Right. - It is far.
Gimpo is closer to my mom's place.
Is that so?
My mother keeps coming to my house.
For the sake of my mother's safety,
I thought I should move closer to her.
It was 2 years ago. I declared it in 2023.
It's my five-year plan to be a good son to my mom.
I'm thinking of breaking ground on my project in Gimpo.
The first thing he does is moving.
(Looking determined)
I'm sure you can find simpler tasks...
- to make her happy. - Right.
Taking pictures with your mom should be enough as the first task.
That won't satisfy me.
- What? - It's nothing special.
You want to pull out all the stops?
Yes.
(After winning the Grand Award at the MBC Entertainment Awards, )
(Moomoo became the variety show princess.)
(And he made a new resolution for his next goal.)
(Fulfilling his duty as a son)
(He gave himself 5 years to complete the project.)
My five years aren't up.
(Afterward, time moved quickly.)
You made that promise a long time ago.
(And 2025 has come.)
(My mother comes to my house.)
(I pile up all the dirty dishes then.)
(Appalled)
(His will to be a good son continued to burn brightly.)
The icon of a bad son.
(He watched how other members fulfilled their duty as children.)
When I watched these clips,
- I learned a lot. - Of course. My gosh.
She comes to my house once every two weeks.
She comes so often.
My house is already clean, but she comes to clean anyway.
"I doubt you did a proper job of cleaning."
(Cleaning)
She doesn't believe in the robot vacuum cleaner.
There's no point. She'll come and clean my house herself anyway.
There's no point in washing the dishes.
She takes out all the plates and washes them again.
That's why I decided to pile them up.
"Okay. Go ahead."
Seriously. She really does that. It drives me crazy.
I called two of my friends...
and deep-cleaned my house. It was spotless.
There wasn't a speck of dust.
But she still came and complained the house was dirty.
And she cleaned all over again.
Moms have a different cleaning standard...
- than we do. - It's a bit different.
- Right. - It's totally different.
I think she does that, so she can be part of your life.
- That's true. - Right.
I thought this would be too much work on my mom.
But I think it's some kind of itch.
It's impossible to talk to her about this.
Living close to her is the best way to fulfill my duty as her son.
- Hey. Then... - Yes.
Do you have any advice for me?
Or do you want to come and check out my house briefly?
Okay. I'm on my way then.
(Okay, I'm in.)
- Now? - Yes.
- Text me the address. - Sure.
Gosh, Gimpo is nice.
(I have a good feeling about this.)
(He then makes another call.)
Sook.
Hyun Moo. Where are you now?
- I... - A lot of celebrities live there.
- She used to live there, but not now. - Right.
I'm going to Gimpo to look at houses. I told you.
Oh, yes. Right. You did.
- I was on the phone with By 100. - Yes.
- Yes. You must ask us about Gimpo. - He...
Right. That's why I called you before I checked out some houses.
You can buy a house toward Mount Modam.
Mount Modam?
But what kind of house do you want?
I've lived in all kinds of houses.
I first moved into an apartment...
- in Gimpo. - Okay.
- Then I lived in a rooftop house. - Okay.
Lastly, I lived in a house with a yard.
Right.
People say they move to Gimpo first before moving to the countryside.
You lived on the rooftop, but it wasn't satisfying.
- You moved to a house with a yard. - Right.
You have to check out the houses and then make a decision.
- Okay. - Yes.
Good luck with house hunting.
- Okay. Thank you. Okay. - Call me if you have questions.
Gosh, why is it raining?
It's pouring down. Come on.
(He starts to see some houses now.)
(Pop-eyed)
This place doesn't look like Korea.
It looks like houses you'd see in "Surprise Mystery TV."
Gosh, nice.
I've never been to a place like that.
My gosh. I had no idea there was a place like this.
This must be the one.
(He arrives at By 100's house.)
(Looking around)
This is the one.
I'm just barging into his house.
- I see. - That's By 100's house?
- Yes, it's his house. - It looks like a house from abroad.
This is the kind of house you'd see abroad.
It's better than I thought.
- Hey, Mr. By 100. - Yes.
(Chuckling)
You're here.
- You were sleeping for real. - Yes.
I was home anyway. So it's no big deal.
Come on in.
My gosh, look at your house. It looks great.
- He decorated his place so nicely. - Look at this.
- He's stylish, to begin with. - He's stylish.
He has a good eye for interior design.
(He fills the house with soft lights from indirect lighting.)
(Boosting the hip vibe with unique props)
Your house has a nice vibe. That's Chet Baker.
- This was a surprise visit. - Yes.
- I'm checking out houses... - Okay.
- in different areas. - Okay.
- You already checked out places. - I called Sook earlier.
- I got a lot of advice from her. - There's also...
a new residential housing complex.
- I don't know. - The one with a yard.
- I don't know. - You don't?
- No. - So that's one of the options.
I also saw a few red-brick houses.
My mother's house is close from here.
It will be easier for my mother to visit me.
She likes having a vegetable garden.
But both of us live in apartments.
I'm serious about this.
- I kept telling you about this. - Yes.
- So you're serious? - Yes.
(Come on.)
(The homeowner is still sleepy as he just woke up.)
He lost a lot of his linguistic skills.
- Well... - Can you give me a tour?
- Of my house? - Yes.
- You don't mind, right? - Sure.
This is the living room. That's the kitchen.
He has a beautiful home.
That's the laundry room. Do you call that a pantry?
- Sure. Probably. - I have a room there.
- Then I have a yard. - Where's the yard?
It's in the back here.
There's a yard in the front.
I love yards.
It used to be full of grass. But I cleared it out.
- That's what you want the most. - Yes.
But I put in tiles this year.
Okay. So you have plants here. This is your garden.
Isn't that great? No one can see you.
It must be easy to manage the space.
It used to be full of grass before.
- But I got rid of it. - I see.
- You got rid of it and added tiles? - I did. Right.
- Yes. It used to have... - You have barbecue parties here.
Yes.
And I grow my plants here.
- Okay. Darn birds? - Those darn birds...
ate up all of my blueberries, so I covered them up.
But they ate through the net.
- He's... - So I have nothing there.
They ripped the net while I was in Sydney.
- They must find food somehow. - Right.
- This place is great. - Yes.
- Yes. - So that's the yard.
- If you want a nice view, - Yes.
You can draw the curtains open. Come here.
(Come this way.)
The mountain is over there.
Is this Mount Modam?
Yes, it is.
- How nice. - It's a floor-to-ceiling window.
The view looks great when it rains and snows.
- I bet. - Yes.
- This window is like a frame. - Yes.
What I liked the most about his house was the greenery.
Trees were everywhere.
- Greenery relaxes me. - You do need that.
I don't care if those birds eat all of my crops.
I can buy blueberries from supermarkets.
Wouldn't it be happier to watch the birds?
Right. The chirping sounds are great too.
I'd welcome animals with open arms.
But you must be ready to face bugs too.
- Right. - Are you okay with bugs?
I'll call a pest-control service.
- I'll exterminate them. - That won't be enough.
- What do I have to do then? - Never.
- That won't do it. - Here's why.
Those services find the source...
- and get rid of the source. - Yes.
- But the source is... - At places like that,
- they just come in from outside. - Right.
- Like friends coming over. - Can't I just raise a frog?
My gosh.
I even thought about that.
- You'll need 2,000 frogs. - What's that?
- Like Venus flytraps. - Gosh, no.
- They won't help? - Not even close.
You need to trap your house with them then.
Can't I just have some house centipedes?
- So... - They'll form a colony.
No. The house centipedes are the weakest bugs...
- They're the nicest ones. - of all the bugs found at homes.
Other bugs that prey on them will come in.
- Like what? - Other centipedes.
- Centipedes. - Scolopendridae with red horns.
- Right. - My gosh.
(That's so scary.)
- Can I go upstairs? - Sure, you can.
(Happily allowing)
(Amazed)
- So this is how it looks upstairs. - This house is great...
for one person.
(At the end of the staircase from the living room, )
(the 2nd-floor space stretches out long.)
(I see!)
This is the master bedroom.
- This is the master bedroom? - Yes.
So...
(Approving)
- Isn't that great? - It's nice and compact.
Yes.
The ceiling is made of glass here.
I can look at the mountain while having a cup of coffee here.
- Yes. - Then I can see the sky.
- I love this. - I see.
There's a skylight window.
- This is nice. - Yes.
Nice.
- This is the main room. - Yes.
This place is nice. I'm curious about upstairs.
- Gosh, it suddenly got so hot. - Right.
I use this place as storage. I haven't cleaned it up yet.
- The layout is quite unique. - I see.
So this is the rooftop. Gosh, it's hot.
I didn't manage this part of the house.
This is what happens when you don't manage it.
- This happens to your yard. - I see. This happens then.
- You have to clear it out. Right. - Yes.
- My yard looks like that. - I see.
See? Do you think you can manage this?
I loved it.
I can pick some vegetables in the morning like Ja Yeon.
I can pick them on the spot and make a salad.
That's the perfect house for that kind of lifestyle.
I'll grow chili peppers and cilantro.
I must also grow arugula and basil. That's for sure.
I must add them when I make pasta and pizza.
I should grow cherry tomatoes too.
It's the vegetable garden I've been longing to have.
Isn't this great?
I didn't know he wanted a vegetable garden.
You know what? I'll give him two months after he moves.
- I won't even give him that long. - I'll give him two weeks.
- You just want that vibe. - Right.
You must spend all of your time on your days off in the garden.
I don't care.
Having a garden is nothing like growing plants at home.
You can give me good tips.
I'll invite Kian84 and get him to work.
We can stop him all we want,
- but he must experience it himself. - You know what?
If I have them at home, they just rot or die.
So I'll keep them outside.
It's like how Ok Ja Yeon eats her own crop.
If you keep them inside, they rot.
- But they'll dry up outside. - Right.
- I'll hire someone to manage it. - So...
Why don't you rent a house and live there for a few months?
- Right. - Yes.
- Live there for six months. - Try it out.
- Just for six months. - It's better...
- to rent 1st in the countryside. - You won't last 6 months.
- He'll never last six months. - Right.
Then can't you just live with your mother?
- She can move to Samseong-dong. - You can bring her...
- to Gangnam. - That's not a good idea.
She has her own social circle.
- Right. - That's true.
- He has a point. - If she moves to Gangnam,
she can't hang out with the mothers...
- of my high school friends. - Right. My mom retired.
- But she can't move to Seoul. - Right.
Social circles are a huge factor.
- But... - That's true.
- That's right. - Daegu is far from Seoul.
- But Gimpo isn't that far. - No. It's not the same.
- Aren't those cases different? - No.
- They don't want to leave. - Moms aren't like that.
- Right. - Really?
- I'll help you. - I'll check out other options.
- Yes. - This place is on my list.
- Really? - Yes. I like it.
Here's what's for sure. It's great for one person.
- Okay. - First of all,
- privacy is great here. - Okay.
- Good privacy. - And it's safe.
The maintenance fee is cheap.
- The maintenance fee is cheap. - Yes.
- It has many amenities. - Right.
There's a mountain nearby.
Right. I love that. Mountain in the back, river in the front.
Yes. Wait. What do you mean?
- You don't know feng shui? - No.
- I know mountains are great. - Okay.
Then we need a water source. Is there an ocean here? I mean...
- There's a river. - There is, right?
- So it has great feng shui. - I see.
So this house is great in that sense.
Okay. Thank you.
Sure.
Are you going to see more houses?
- Yes. I must get going. - I see. Okay.
Thank you.
- I know this was quite sudden. - Gosh, don't mention it.
- Bye. Thanks. - Bye, Hyun Moo.
- Bye. - Bye, Hyun Moo.
- Okay. Number 1. - Number 1.
Hello, this is the real estate office.
Hello, ma'am. This is Jun Hyun Moo.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Are you there now? - Yes.
- Yes, I'm here. - I'll be there shortly.
Okay.
Everyone has been living a colorful life.
(He sets out to carry out the house-hunting schedule.)
There she is.
(Popping out)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Realtor Kim Eun Su)
- It's raining today. - Right.
- Thank you. I'll carry that. - Okay.
- Sure. Let's carry it together. - Okay.
- I guess this unit is vacant. - Yes, it is.
- I see. Is this the one? - So...
Yes. This is the one.
- Let's go inside. - Okay.
Isn't that the same as By 100's?
It's in a different complex. But it's the same house.
- This is supported by pilotis. - I see.
- Gosh, this is nice too. - Yes, it is.
- It's a communal area. - No.
- What? - It's a private area for the unit.
- This is the first floor? - Yes.
- It's great then. - It's not a communal area?
No. The whole building...
- is one house. - Really?
- That's great. - Isn't it?
- It's not a shared space. - No.
- Gosh. - This is nice.
- I can throw parties here. - And...
- it has folding doors. - That's right.
- Gosh, this is nice. - That must be fun.
It's different from By 100's house.
You can set it up like a cafe.
- I can grill pork belly here. - Sure. You can do that too.
Him and his pork belly.
- It's enclosed for privacy. - Yes.
There's also a side door to the back.
- There's a side door. - Yes.
I have some extra space here.
This is nice.
It feels like a separate house too.
- There are always staircases here. - Yes.
The living area starts on the second floor.
I see.
- This is the foyer. - The foyer.
This place is beautiful.
- How beautiful. - The living room and the kitchen.
They're beautifully set up.
The view here...
- There's a small pocket balcony. - I see.
You can partially see Mount Modam from here.
The previous house I checked out...
- overlooked Mount Modam in full. - I see.
So the view here is disappointing in comparison.
At By 100's house, I could see the entire mountain.
- But since it's on the far end, - It's more private.
- That's the upside, right? - it's private. Yes.
That unit is more expensive since it faces Mount Modam, right?
(He's still hung up on it.)
Right. It's more expensive...
- with a better view. - Right?
You can't have everything.
- The living room and the kitchen. - Yes.
Okay. Let's go upstairs and look.
This is the third floor.
- The third floor? - Yes.
This is the main room.
- Yes. - The master bedroom.
Lastly, there's the fourth floor.
We have to climb up again.
You can't live in a separate house without stairs.
Of course not.
It's okay if the living area is on the first floor.
- Right. - If you can easily come and go.
- Let's say you're going abroad. - If you have luggage.
Think about carrying your suitcase...
up and down.
- Seriously. It drives you crazy. - It would.
- Seriously. - Can't I keep the suitcase...
on the first floor?
- You can do that. - Wait.
- But you must pack. - Bringing his stuff down...
- Yes. - and packing his suitcases there?
Or bring all of your stuff to the first floor.
People with a lot of stuff should live in a house like that.
- It's for people like them. - That's true.
- My previous house is... - My gosh.
The closest match to the unit we're seeing now.
- Yes. - To this house.
My bedroom was on the top floor,
- the fourth floor. - Yes.
Personally, I loved walking down...
to the basement after waking up.
- So... - I'd be scared...
in case someone might be there.
Then just keep living in Samseong-dong.
But this unit doesn't have a place for a vegetable garden.
- If you want to do that, - Yes?
You can set it up here.
This is enough space.
- This place is great. - Yes.
- It's quite spacious. - You can set up a home cafe too.
- This is big enough. - Right.
- The view is nice. - Yes.
- I can throw parties here. - Yes.
- I rarely throw parties, though. - Him and his darn parties.
How many parties will he throw?
- Those darn pork belly parties. - You rarely throw parties.
This unit had a different charm from By 100's unit.
His house had a better view.
But when it comes to socializing areas...
where I can hang out with people, this unit wins.
The extra space on the first floor.
I'll throw barbecue parties there.
- That's nice. - I like this part of the house.
- We can have gatherings there. - Yes.
There are balconies in the front and back.
How long does it take from here to Sangam-dong?
From what I know, it takes 30 minutes without traffic.
- Thirty minutes? - It's not that close.
- Right. - But if there's traffic,
it takes longer than an hour.
- An hour? - Yes.
That's how long it takes from my current place.
- Yeouido is farther, right? - Yes.
It takes about 30 to 40 minutes too.
That's how long it takes from Samseong-dong.
How long does it take from your mom's place?
- Right. That's important. - To my mom's place, it will take...
about 20 minutes.
- It is close. - Yes.
- What about from your place? - It takes a long time.
- I bet it takes long. - She must take Olympic-daero.
I feel anxious when I hear she's coming over.
- I see. - Right.
Okay. I think I've seen enough.
Okay.
Let's go to the next house.
- Sure. - Okay.
Where should I go?
Unyang-dong.
- Is it a townhouse? - Yes.
- I'm looking forward to this one. - Really?
They only tease you with the first house.
- Right. - Yes.
- It gets better toward the end. - Really?
- They get more expensive too. - At the end, they say,
- "I wasn't going to show you this." - Right, at the end.
You guys are spot on.
You'll soon see an excellent house.
- Really? - I'm 100 percent sure.
It's the red-bricked house over there.
- That red-bricked house? - Yes.
- It stands out. - Yes.
(They arrive at a red-brick house.)
This is the house.
It does stand out.
- As I told you... - Is that also part of the house?
- Yes. They make up one unit. - Really?
- It's not a duplex? - What?
- Gosh, that's big. - It's unique, isn't it?
- So the whole thing is one house? - Yes.
- They're connected. - Gosh, that's cool.
Let's go inside and take a look.
- They used unique bricks too. - I see.
How beautiful.
- This unit is occupied now, right? - Yes.
- Excuse me. - Okay.
- That's such an awkward moment. - Yes, it is.
- It feels like you must be quick. - Yes.
- Let's go inside and look. - Okay.
(They enter the house past the foyer door.)
Gosh. What?
(The long hallway is overwhelming.)
My gosh, that's beautiful.
When the homeowner built the house,
- a lot of care went into it. - I see.
(Following the hallway, )
(a tidy white living room is revealed.)
- This house is spacious. - Yes.
I see. It's a circular layout.
(The kitchen has ample space too.)
(The 1st floor is spacious like a mansion.)
- I see how it's set up. - Yes. That's the garden.
- They use this as a yard. - Yes.
- They did a great job. - Right.
(A private garden appears outside the window.)
- How beautiful. - This is great.
Right?
- This whole building is one unit. - Yes, that's right.
It looks like a college building.
It looks like a college campus on the East Coast.
- The homeowner must be neat. - It's beautiful.
The deck is made from basalt.
- Basalt? - A homophone for Hyun Moo?
- How cozy. I see. - I wanted to tell you that.
- It looks very fancy. - Yes.
It's meant for you.
You can see the yard from here.
(He can enjoy the garden from the room.)
Where do I go next?
Let's go upstairs to the second floor.
(They go up the staircase to the 2nd floor.)
This is the second-floor living room.
- The second-floor living room? - Yes.
Check out the ceiling on the second floor.
- It's quite high. - It is, right?
- I can set it up as a gym... - Right. It's great for that.
- although I won't. - Okay.
You don't seem to love the house.
- He's not impressed by it. - Right.
- This is the secondary room. - The secondary room.
Yes, this is how the secondary room looks.
(There's another room.)
I can see that he's lost interest.
I think their son uses this room.
And there's a built-in closet.
(I see.)
My blood sugar was crashing then.
As for the second house I checked out,
the realtor recommended it for me.
The house itself is beautiful.
The ceiling is high too.
But it was too big for one person.
She must've thought I wanted a big house.
I think that's why she showed me that house.
I don't think I can make use of all that space.
If I were married or had my own family,
that would've been a great house since all the rooms...
- and spaces are separated. - Right.
Each room would provide privacy.
Had they cut the two brick houses with a knife and said,
"Take this side,"
I would've given it a serious thought.
- Give the other side to your mom. - No!
That's right. You can give it to your mom.
Then she'll live close to you.
- That's right. - Then I'll set up an iron gate.
(Then I'll set up an iron gate.)
I'll set up an iris recognition system.
The door won't open to my mom's iris.
Wasn't this a project about being a filial son?
You're moving because you want to.
- Don't use your mom as an excuse. - Your mom is just an excuse.
- Living together won't be an issue. - You want to enjoy country life.
But she visits often anyway.
Breaking ground on the project of being a filial son?
If I live alone,
there'll be spaces I don't even use once...
in two years.
It looked nice at first.
It isn't easy to check out the houses.
My blood sugar crashed.
(He drives to the next house in a sluggish state.)
- We're nearly there. - Yes.
Go down to the underground parking lot.
- This one? - Yes.
It's an apartment.
Yes, it's built like an apartment.
- It's Kim Sook's place. - That's right.
- I see. - It's a mix...
- of an apartment and a townhouse. - It's in the middle.
- That's right. - Really?
- Is there such a thing? - The benefits are combined.
Coming to the parking lot of an apartment...
puts my mind at ease.
- That's right. - I've lived there all my life.
That's right.
(How will the house be?)
- Let's go inside. - It's still Christmas.
- All right. Let's go inside. - Excuse me.
- It's a typical house. - This is the entrance.
Let's go inside and look.
This is a bathroom.
- It's similar to your place. - It's nice.
That's right.
There used to be another room.
They added this much space to the living room
- They brought down the walls. - Yes. So, the living room is big.
- The living room is really big. - You could have a party.
You're obsessed with parties.
There's enough space for a party.
Let's take a look at the kitchen.
- When you do the dishes, - Yes?
You can see the Han River if you look out the window.
It's the Han River view.
- You can see it. - You can see it.
- You can see it well. - It's the partial Han River view.
(My mom will be able to see the Han River.)
The caption reflects my heart.
Nothing obstructs the view, so it's refreshing.
You'll see that better once you go to the upper level.
I'm actually here because of the upper level.
That's right.
I'll open the door.
- Look at that. - I see.
There's a staircase.
- You can go up the stairs. - Okay.
Shall we go?
- This place is incredible. - Right?
(Impressed)
It's the top floor.
- It's the top floor. - Yes.
(You can go up another level through the staircase.)
It's the attic.
It's Wonderland.
- The living room. - Yes, this is...
- the living room. - You can play here.
That's right.
- And... - This is it.
Yes, this is it.
(This is it.)
- This is what you wanted. - That's it.
Kian84 washed his bottoms at a place like that.
- Oh, my. - You know,
- it's very big. - It's big.
- Here. - That's right. This is it.
I don't have a place like this.
(Moomoo hurriedly goes outside.)
The terrace is pretty spacious, right?
Gosh, this is number one.
- Look at that. - The floor is pretty.
- It's nice. - It's spacious.
- It's nice. - Look at the garden.
- You can grow arugula and basil. - Yes.
It's really nice.
- Right? - It's quite private.
And...
- Yes. - This place is number one.
- This is it. - This place...
This place...
We aren't done yet.
- We aren't done yet. There's... - What's this?
- Is there more? - There's a secret observatory.
- There's a secret observatory. - What's this?
- There's that feature. - There's a summit.
Yes.
Let's check out the observatory.
My goodness.
What's the use of hiking?
The view of the Han River stretches before you.
Look at that. Isn't it like the Netherlands?
The view of the Han River.
It's nice. It's so nice.
I wanted something like this.
A space for myself with an open view.
- That was what I wanted. - That's right.
- I can see the entire Han River. - Look at that.
When the weather is nice, you can sit on a bench...
- You're right. - and have a cup of tea.
- I can see the Eiffel Tower. - The Eiffel Tower?
(I can see the Eiffel Tower.)
- Is that the Eiffel Tower? - The Eiffel Tower!
The Eiffel Tower has shrunk significantly in size.
- It's perfect. - Among the places I've seen today,
this one is the best.
I knew you'd say that.
- I love the open view. - Yes.
He likes it.
This place is number one. I love this place.
When I went up from the underground parking lot...
and went through the entrance,
I felt like it was too similar to my current place.
But the new world unfolded as soon as I went up the stairs.
It was like entering through Platform 9 and 1-Quarter...
- in "Harry Potter." - It's Platform 9 and 3-Quarters.
It was like a different dimension.
It was like seeing the flipped world in "Inception."
That was how shocking it was.
When I went up another staircase, it felt like...
- I was at the Florence Cathedral. - The Florence Cathedral?
When the sun sets around 5pm, the cool autumn breeze blows,
(The autumn breeze blows at 5pm.)
and the church bells ring, you can look down...
at Florence and get the same feeling.
- It's quiet, - That's the feeling.
But you get some sounds of people.
For the place that resembles the top of the Florence Cathedral,
I'll spend the most amount of money for interior design.
- He'll make a deposit. - He loves it so much.
He'll make a deposit.
I'll decorate it so that it looks like an observatory.
It might be overdone, but I must hang up some lightbulbs.
- It'll be like a cafe in Euljiro. - A cafe in Euljiro?
I must do that.
You know the carpets from Nepal and Bhutan, right?
I must set them up.
(Adding the carpets with the vibes of Nepal and Bhutan)
You know what I mean, right?
At the terrace?
For goodness' sake.
In winter,
it'll be great if I set up an electric heater.
When it ends, it'll totally be the Santa Claus Village in Finland.
(It'll totally be the Santa Claus Village in Finland.)
It represents all the nations.
So, which nation is it in the end?
It's Mexico.
- Mexico? - Mexico?
You didn't even mention Mexico before.
It isn't important. In any case, it's like that.
I'll set up a Christmas tree too.
He's excited.
It'll be up there.
It'll totally be like the Florence Cathedral.
I'll call it the Moorence Cathedral.
The Moorence Cathedral?
You don't even go to church.
I can go to one from now on.
This country has freedom of religion.
Yes, it does.
I'll give it a go.
- It's good. - Okay.
(He comes down from the Moorence Cathedral.)
I see.
That's right. I can change up the interior design.
Yes.
The living room is spacious.
(It looks even nicer now.)
- I enjoyed the tour. - Thank you.
He's leaning toward this place.
Please give me a call if there's a property you like.
- I'll give you a call. Thank you. - Okay.
I'm keeping in touch with the real estate agent.
Before buying your current place, how many times did you visit?
I didn't do many visits.
- What? - Really?
- Not even for your current place? - No.
- It's a must for buying a place. - How did you buy a place...
without visiting it?
I have a story about my current place.
That place was my dream house.
- Some places are like that. - It was like that from the start.
- It's entirely possible. - When I was an announcer,
I worked as a reporter for "Entertainment Weekly."
- Back then... - You visited the house back then.
Back then, I covered a story on Kwon Sang Woo...
and Son Tae Young's dating rumors.
- They're married now. - Yes.
So I visited the apartment one of them lived in.
Was it Kwon Sang Woo's place?
- It was a long time ago. - Seriously.
It's an old story.
I'm in front of his house.
- His face is full of greed. - Yes.
- He was a baby. - He's full of ambition.
"Hello, I'm here to cover a story..."
- "on the popular dating rumor." - It's an old story.
"I'll go inside."
Then the security guard went, "You can't enter."
That was what we filmed.
That's right. We filmed such scenes back in the day.
Right?
"Will I be able to live in such a place one day?"
- I had that thought all my life. - It became a goal.
Thus, it was my first time checking out multiple properties.
- It was so exhausting. - It's so exhausting.
This isn't easy. I can't make up my mind.
I'm hungry.
My goodness.
(Suppressing his hunger, he arrives at a place.)
(Groaning)
I'm exhausted.
It isn't easy to visit properties.
Why am I so exhausted?
(He enters a place in an exhausted state.)
- Hello. - Hello.
It smells nice.
- Sook, lastly, - Okay.
Recommend me a good restaurant in Gimpo.
She knows many good restaurants.
Do you like sujebi?
Eat there. It's so tasty. They sell sujebi.
- That sounds nice. - Sook is like a machine.
If I actually move here,
good restaurants will be important.
It'll be important to live near the good restaurants.
So I asked a Gimpo resident, Kim Sook.
It's a big achievement.
This is nice.
Kim Sook recommended the place to me.
- Thank you. - She said it was a good restaurant.
I wanted to eat sujebi,
- but it starts from 2 servings. - Yes. It starts from 2 servings.
- Okay. I'll order two servings. - There you go.
What else should I eat?
This restaurant is famous for grilled half-dried pollack...
and barley rice.
Good. I'll get them.
- I'll cook them well. - Okay.
Thank you.
(He enters a restaurant after visiting several properties.)
(A huge pot of sujebi appears.)
What's that?
- It looks so tasty. - This is insane.
(His eyes go wide.)
(Grilled half-fried pollack is served next.)
- Grilled half-fried pollack. - I'm busy looking at the dishes.
(There is barley rice as well as seasoned vegetables.)
This is exciting.
(It's a hearty meal of Korean dishes.)
I like this place the most.
You should pick this place.
The living room is spacious.
The kitchen is spacious too.
- It's perfect for partying. - You're right.
I'll be able to invite about 250 people.
There are aunties too.
You could put the chairs together and sleep on them.
It'll be like a stone bed.
It'll be nice.
(The party enthusiast begins eating at the property he visited.)
(He starts eating the grilled half-dried pollack.)
- He's making a perilla leaf wrap... - Half-dried pollack.
- with the half-dried pollack. - It looks moist.
(Eating)
The half-dried pollack was both moist and tender.
The half-dried pollack dish is so tasty.
Gosh, look at the shrimp.
- It contains freshwater shrimp. - That's right.
- That's right. - My goodness.
- It contains doenjang. - Yes.
- It's homemade doenjang. - That's right.
- It looks really delicious. - It's bound to be tasty.
(He tries the soup reverently.)
(My goodness)
It's so tasty.
Gosh, the shrimp...
(Eating hurriedly)
Just pick this place.
- It's one of the candidates. - This is the best place.
The shrimp provides the kick.
(He immediately makes the barley rice bibimbap.)
Forget about finding a house.
(He pours in all the seasoned vegetables.)
- Pour in everything. - That's it.
Seasoned vegetables don't make you gain weight.
It looks delicious.
(Glossy)
(He takes a big spoonful.)
(He inhales the food quickly.)
Barley rice.
Drink the sujebi soup when food blocks your throat.
That's it.
- You speak as if you've watched me. - Yes.
(Drinking)
It's so refreshing.
(He forgets about the stressful task of checking out the properties.)
(He shoves food down his throat.)
- My eyes began to go crazy then. - I can see that.
It's so tasty.
Sook, thank you.
He's eating with gusto.
(He shoves in the taste of Gimpo without a thought.)
I feel better now.
I was starving earlier.
Ma'am.
Would you please pack this to go?
- Shall I do that? - Yes.
- I'll pack it to go. - Thank you.
(He packs the leftover sujebi to go.)
(Sweating)
(He inhaled 4 servings of food.)
- He enjoyed the food. - He really enjoyed it.
I'm drowsy.
(He calls someone after finishing his meal.)
Hello.
Hello. What is it?
- It's his mom. - It's his mom.
What?
Where are you?
- Hello? - I'm in the neighborhood.
- Are you in the neighborhood? - Yes. Why?
- Today... - Today?
- Today, I visited Gimpo... - Okay.
(Burping)
Why are you burping so much while talking to your mom?
It just came out.
You could've called her after you were done.
- I didn't want to forget. - Okay.
I checked out some townhouses.
Okay.
- For goodness' sake. - I plan to rent out...
- my apartment in Samseong-dong. - Okay.
I'm worried since you're forgetful these days.
Okay.
I'm thinking about moving to Gimpo. What do you think about that?
- Us? - Are you telling her now?
- Didn't you tell her before? - No, I didn't.
It was a surprise. Had I told her, she would've been against it.
So, I wanted to tell her once things had progressed somewhat.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I'm thinking about moving to Gimpo. What do you think about that?
- Us? - Me.
You want to move to Gimpo?
What do you think about that?
I'll be 30 minutes away from your place.
It'll be nice.
Will it be nice?
I was surprised because it was an unexpected answer.
It'll be the best for us.
It'll be reassuring to have you around.
How does the place look?
It looks handsome.
Handsome?
I'll need to look into it more.
So you aren't against me moving to Gimpo, right?
I'm not against it, but it might be hard on you.
It'll be hard on me.
I'm doing this for you.
- Is that so? - Yes.
If it's hard on you, I'm not sure about it.
- You... - It won't benefit me.
- Then you shouldn't do it. - It'll be hard on me,
but it'll be okay since the TV stations are...
in Sangam-dong and Yeouido.
No, don't do it.
You should stay there. We'll travel to see you.
She changed her word since I said that it'd be hard on me.
Why did you boast about it?
You shouldn't tell your mom things like, "This is expensive."
"I went through much trouble to get it."
Moms don't like that.
I regretted making that comment.
I was like, "Why did I say that?"
I think she's actually happy about it.
- Seriously. - If you don't come to my place...
at times...
to do the dirty dishes and vacuum the floor,
I won't need to do this.
But you come to my place even when I tell you not to.
- My place is too far, - You regretted making that comment.
So I feel bad about you traveling all the way there.
- You just have to do those things. - No. That's...
We feel comfortable when we see traces of you.
When we're by ourselves,
we feel like we're at a Buddhist temple.
So, don't feel bad about my visits.
If you move to Gimpo, the long commute will wear you down.
- You need to think about that. - In any case,
I take it that you're okay with the idea.
- You're okay... - I'm not okay with the idea.
- No. - It won't be hard on me.
I want to try living in a townhouse.
Be quiet.
- I'll grow chili peppers. - Stop spouting nonsense.
Don't move to Gimpo.
Hello?
Why did I tell her that it'd be hard on me?
Firstly, I'll look more into the house in Gimpo...
I'll check it out more today with my real estate agent.
I'll talk to my mom more.
If she's really against me moving to Gimpo,
I could move her to that house.
I'll need to think about different ideas.
I'll need to take a careful approach for this project of filial duty.
She has made so many sacrifices in her life.
I don't want to think about me.
I want her to be a selfish mom who only thinks about herself.
Your life should be centered around you,
not us.
- You need to build your life. - Even if I move to Gimpo,
my life will be centered around me.
While I know that,
you need to get married. I'm against it.
- In any case, stay there. - Is marriage impossible in Gimpo?
Don't sell your current house. Since you became successful there,
you should hold on to it.
I won't decide today. In any case, I'll show you some properties.
Be quiet.
You aren't getting married.
- Be quiet. Then... - All right.
Don't get hurt.
- Okay. - She always says, "Don't get hurt."
Gosh.
I'm getting an upset stomach.
I'm getting an upset stomach because of Mom.
(The 47 Year Old Who Is Still Childish)
- I think that's filial love. - Really?
- Same here. - You usually don't keep in touch.
Talking about that is filial love.
You're right.
Then say a few words to your mom.
(Well...)
Firstly,
I didn't mean anything when I said that it'd be hard on me.
I've been dreaming of living in a place like that,
so please know that I'm doing this for myself.
- That's right. - Since you live nearby,
it's like killing 2 birds with 1 stone.
I'm not sacrificing myself for you and Dad.
Please understand that.
I'm not saying this for your sake.
- That's right. - Why didn't you say that...
on the phone?
- That's right. - That's right.
Hyun Moo, tell her that you love her.
- No. - Say it.
"I love you."
My mom will be uncomfortable.
- Why would she be uncomfortable? - Shall I say it in your stead?
- Shall I say it in your stead? - You should say it.
Ma'am, Hyun Moo loves you.
- What's this? - He loves you.
Even I feel embarrassed.
Tell your mom that you love her.
I can't do it.
- See? - Say it in his stead.
- Say it in his stead. - I can't do it.
Kian84's mom, Kian84 loves you as always.
- Oh, my. - What's this?
- Kian84 loves you. - What's this?
Please stay healthy.
Ko Kang Yong, welcome.
- It has been a while. - Hello.
- It has been a while. - My goodness.
Isn't it the 1st meeting for the 2 of you?
- Kang Yong and MINHO. - It's nice to meet you.
I watched your episode. It's our first time meeting.
I watched your episode too.
I thought we were similar in many ways.
In what ways?
There's alertness in his eyes.
It's natural to go overboard at that stage in his career.
While ramyeon was cooking,
- you took a shower. - Yes.
(MINHO's passionate ramyeon challenge)
After a workout,
I thaw a pack of chicken breast...
while taking a shower. I do it at times.
- Some people live like this. - That's right.
It's one of the traits that's shown by people...
who work out early in the morning.
(For goodness' sake)
- I have good news. - What is it?
- His solo album came out. - My goodness.
It came out after three years.
- That's impressive. - It came out.
You're preparing for solo promotions.
The album came out already.
- It came out today. - It came out today.
- Okay. - The music video got released.
- Give us the title. - It's "HUNTER."
- "HUNTER." - "HUNTER."
- It's an intense title. - I like it.
(Will You Recharge Yourself?)
"Will You Recharge Yourself?"
It looks like he's enveloped in a blanket.
(It's quiet inside the room.)
(Kang Yong is recharging his energy.)
Do you like PSG? Are you a PSG fan?
- I went to France. - I see.
As I was buying Lee Kang In's uniform,
- I decided to get that too. - How did you know that?
Where does it say that?
It's next to Wilson.
- It's next to Wilson. - I see.
- Wasn't that the logo for Pepsi? - No.
That's the logo for Paris Saint-Germain F.C.
- That was seen as Pepsi? - Wasn't it Domino's Pizza?
Wasn't that the box for Domino's Pizza?
Only CODE KUNST, MINHO, and I noticed it.
- I see. - Just the soccer fans.
- Aren't you just a human fan? - Human fan?
Human fan.
(Kang Yong is still in dreamland.)
So this place doesn't have blackout curtains.
- Right. - I didn't think I could wake up...
with blackout curtains.
- I couldn't put them up. - There are people like that.
Right.
(He was able to get up due to the lack of blackout curtains.)
Hello. I'm MBC's announcer, Ko Kang Yong.
Announcer Ko Kang Yong.
(MBC's rookie announcer that has entered less than a year ago)
(Hello.)
(Passionate as a rookie)
(And...)
(his down-to-earth home got a lot of attention.)
It's an old house.
(He was like a relatable friend. I wish to see more of him.)
(It was interesting to watch as it was realistic.)
(Relatable as a K-Office Worker)
- A lot of people felt sympathy. - Right.
How was it after being on the show?
First of all, a lot of people recognized me.
I went to a kalguksu place and the old lady owner...
kept asking if I was the one on I Live Alone.
- She even gave me free dumplings. - My gosh!
Free dumplings mean so much.
- She kept telling me to come back. - Gosh, dumplings?
I gave a lot of autographs too.
After being on I Live Alone,
my parents changed their profile pictures...
to a scene from my appearance on the show.
(His mother's actual profile)
This is what my mother did.
Reruns of the show are shown every day throughout the week.
- Right. - She watched all of the reruns.
My goodness.
- That isn't easy to do. - That isn't easy to do.
"Why write so much in your journal as a young man?"
I got a lot of attention from the people around me.
(He got busier as he gained more attention these days.)
(Unlike the busy times he had these days, )
(Is Kang Yong enjoying some free time in bed?)
It was my day off after a while.
It was Saturday,
so I didn't set the alarm.
I allowed myself to sleep until my eyes opened.
No wonder you looked relaxed.
I usually woke up to the alarm on weekdays.
(He worked too hard in the weekdays.)
I wanted to be free from the alarm at least during the weekends.
There are times when my eyes open even without the alarm.
I feel really happy when I get back to sleep...
after knowing it's the weekend.
- Gosh, that's the best feeling. - That's the best feeling.
This happened when I was an announcer.
- It's dark in the winter. - Right.
I used to be on a radio show that was at dawn.
I opened my eyes...
and it was really bright. It felt like it was 9am.
I cried.
I cried like this.
- I cried. - You couldn't do anything...
and you thought you were in big trouble.
- I couldn't look at my phone. - Right.
I just wept right away.
I did this after waking up with no clothes on.
He has a lot of body heat.
It was a Saturday though.
- There are those moments. - You know what I mean, right?
- I definitely know what you mean. - That must've woken you up.
- Office workers go through this. - Right.
(Current time: 10:09am)
(He watches baseball in bed.)
It must be nice to have a day off.
I'm like that too.
I always watch sports highlights too.
MINHO is amazing at baseball.
(MINHO is amazing at baseball.)
(Let's get up and tidy things up.)
You could just leave it alone as it's the weekend.
(He diligently tidies up the bedding even on the weekend.)
(Grabbing)
(He sets up the table.)
(Let's eat first.)
That's the glutinous rice sent from my mother.
She continues to send some over to me.
The egg jangjorim must taste really good.
(When the side dishes get heated up, )
Is it done?
(a breakfast meal is ready right away.)
- That looks good. - That looks good.
- What is that? - What is that?
What is that?
It's braised skate.
- Braised skate? - Braised skate?
(Thank you, Mother.)
She sends a lot of precious dishes.
She sends a lot of food.
- Braised skate is really good. - Braised skate?
- Right. - Have you tried braised skate?
- I've never tried it. - I've never seen it before.
- It's my first time seeing it. - It's really good.
It's good. It tastes clean.
(Relaxed)
(Unlike how he shoved in his food during the weekdays, )
(he looks peaceful during the weekend.)
This is the best thing about weekends.
(After enjoying the food in peace, )
(the bowls get emptied.)
(Let's clean up right away.)
(Groaning)
There's a big pile.
As I was busy during the weekdays,
I usually did the dishes all at once during the weekends.
There must've been around five pairs of chopsticks.
I wasn't able to take care of the dishes at all.
(Let's wash them as it's the weekend.)
(He washes the chopsticks piled up during the weekdays.)
Gosh, there are fruit flies.
(He even has a fruit fly trap set up.)
Gosh, those darn fruit flies.
(Washing with his bare hands)
(He thoroughly tries to dry up the water around the sink.)
(Grabbing)
(Sniffing)
The laundry?
I was just going to wash the towel,
but I could see the things that need to be washed.
You always find them after you start washing them.
- Right. - Right.
- There are those times. - Gosh.
They have to be done at once.
(Current time: 10:57am)
(Thinking)
Gosh, I should take this off.
- What is that? - It's newspaper.
- It's to block the oil. - The oil?
I flip fried eggs often.
I flip them without using a spatula.
That is when the oil splatters.
Gosh, look at the frying pan.
(The oily items are moved.)
(Thinking)
It has the looks of an old restaurant.
Right.
- This wasn't an old restaurant? - Do you clean your place...
every single day?
This is quite clean in my standards.
(This is quite clean in my standards.)
(Snickering)
- That's clean? - It's not that clean...
after looking at it closely.
(Tearing up)
(He sprays the detergent to make it clean.)
(Spraying a generous amount)
That's a tough stain.
I push it back and avoid it,
but there are times when it bothers me.
Let's see.
Rubber gloves? I don't have any.
- You'll use your bare hands? - You don't need them.
That's really strong though.
He's a guy who touches bleach...
- with his bare hands. - Then...
do you touch bleach with your bare hands?
There's no time to think about those things.
In this busy generation,
there's no time to think about those things.
(He's a true bleach rocker.)
I should put these on at least.
(Only human)
(He wears plastic gloves instead of rubber gloves.)
(Rubbing hard)
Gosh, that's nice.
It really wouldn't come off.
It should be done thoroughly while you're at it.
It's working.
Gosh, it's clean.
That was nicely done.
Nice.
What? Hold on.
It's still a bit...
(It doesn't look fully clean.)
- That's good enough. - Right.
- He lives alone too. - Right.
(He gets something else out while he's at it.)
(He starts drawing lines with some sort of chalk.)
I get house centipedes.
It's a type of chalk that you can use to draw lines...
to prevent house centipedes or cockroaches.
House centipedes are beneficial insects though.
- Right. - Those aren't usually killed.
House centipedes.
Those house centipedes eat other insects like roaches.
They do.
But don't they look disgusting?
- They should be left alone. - They look bad,
but they are good guys.
Don't cross over.
(Don't cross over even if you're a good guy.)
(It's my precious home!)
(He uses the lint roller this time.)
The lint roller.
(Sweeping)
(He diligently cleans the areas that are seen.)
The lint roller is the best item at studio apartments.
You can clean everything with the lint roller and wet wipes.
Right.
(It's the weekend, )
(but he even washes the bathroom without any breaks.)
I love those eyes.
What are you doing?
What is that over your eyes?
- It's a sleep mask. - I see.
The light was right above me,
so it hurt my eyes.
Turn off the lights then.
Putting that over my eyes makes it feel like the lights are off.
Based on what standard are announcers picked?
- I wonder. - They must be unique.
- They must be unique? - Yes.
(I've passionately spent my weekend.)
I wasn't planning to spend this much time on cleaning,
but I didn't want to do things during the weekdays...
after coming home from work. I want to rest during weekdays.
I think that was why...
I tried to do everything while I had the energy in the weekend.
I agree.
It doesn't look different from afar.
It's different if you look from up close.
(He feels much better after cleaning.)
(His weekend morning went by quickly with cleaning.)
The Suns?
The Phoenix Suns.
- Kevin Durant. - Right.
I really like...
I remember seeing a KCC uniform too.
Right. Basketball is my favorite.
Weren't you a special commentator before?
- I love basketball too. - Right.
But basketball isn't that popular these days.
Basketball needs to get back up. It isn't that popular these days.
But as our national team...
is doing well in the Asia Cup,
- I expect... - A boom to start?
- a boom to start. - I think the same way too.
We should play basketball sometime.
- Really? - Yes.
- I love basketball. - Definitely.
I'm definitely down for that.
Let's see.
(He's focused on something while being seated.)
What is that?
I have a bit of gray hair.
- Really? - I see.
I sprayed hair fibers before coming today.
I got it from my father.
- But... - Age doesn't matter.
Really?
I dye my hair around once a month or once every three weeks...
because of my gray hair.
That's around 150 dollars spent a month...
just for my hair.
I like getting down perms too.
As I was spending too much,
I thought that I could try dyeing my hair at home.
That was why I gave it a try.
- That should be fine. - It should be done alone.
I heard people with gray hair don't have hair loss.
- They have a lot of hair. - I have gray hair and hair loss.
(I have gray hair and hair loss.)
You're so rich.
- You have everything. - You have everything.
- You have old age too. - Why are you so greedy?
- You have everything. - Gosh.
- I'm jealous. - I didn't want to...
- miss out on anything. - My goodness.
He's so rich.
- Hyun Moo... - He has money,
hair loss, gray hair,
- Chest hair. - chest hair,
and even the Grand Award.
- He has everything. - He has everything.
- He wants to have everything. - Right.
- He really has everything. - That's so impressive.
(The one with a lot of gray hair gets done with making the hair dye.)
(Rustling)
Should I have done it with the gloves on?
(Getting thoroughly prepared to get his hair dyed)
Okay.
(Grabbing)
(Cutting the insulating tape)
(Letting out a sigh)
(The tape was forced to become one with the glove.)
You should just wrap it around the glove when that happens.
- Really? - It will tear up the glove.
- It tore up. - It tore up.
- You can just wrap it around. - It tore up.
(There are even holes in the gloves now.)
Let's just do it.
(I'll just bear with it.)
(He puts on the plastic gown as well.)
I think you'll ruin your shirt.
No. I don't need this.
He doesn't know how to get things done.
You should just wrap your neck with the insulating tape.
With the insulating tape?
(He heads to the bathroom without any tape or gown.)
(Without anything on him, )
(he starts hunting for his gray hair.)
(Instead of spending 150 dollars at the salon...)
It's a hassle to get to the salon.
- Getting there is a hassle too. - Right.
It's such a hassle to get to the salon.
Right.
(He applies a generous amount on the back without looking.)
This is quite risky though.
- That feels nice. - Right. It's just done like that.
You're good.
(The hair dye has been applied neatly.)
For 25 minutes?
Around 2:10pm.
(He reuses the plastic gown as a hair cover.)
Nice.
(He grabs something.)
It's nice that you can do something else...
- Right. - if you do it at home.
He wrote something the other time too.
Something that I want to be grateful for.
- It's my gratitude journal. - Right. The gratitude journal.
Right.
(Kang Yong's long-time habit, writing in his gratitude journal)
(I feel grateful that my parents supported me for 25 years.)
He writes a lot of things.
That's done with a passion.
(He diligently writes in it even on the weekend.)
What will he be grateful for today?
I'm curious about what he'll be grateful about.
(At this moment, what are you grateful for?)
"I am grateful that the hair dye didn't get on my face."
(I am grateful that the hair dye didn't get on my face.)
You're really forcing it out.
- It has to be forced out. - "I am grateful that..."
"I can spend a cool summer with the air conditioner."
Imagine being without the air conditioner.
- It would be extremely hot. - We should all feel grateful.
I think the second one is something we all should be grateful for.
(It's time to wash his hair after being grateful.)
Gosh.
(Groaning)
(He rubs the hair dye on the wall with his bare hands.)
Kang Yong isn't that neat either.
(His smartness is slightly lacking.)
Gosh.
(He almost washed his hair with the plastic.)
(Gosh!)
It didn't splatter that much when I washed my hair.
That's normal for everyone.
As I might get hair loss,
I should wash my hair with the anti-hair loss shampoo.
That's good.
If only I had met that earlier.
(A great amount of foam)
(He washes his hair thoroughly and refreshingly.)
(Shaking)
(He's satisfied with his hair.)
(He uses the hairdryer right away.)
(My bangs are precious.)
There's a lot of volume.
It turned out really well,
so I felt really satisfied.
- Gosh. - It's like it was done at a salon.
You know how to dye your hair well.
(He brings up his confidence with his neat hair.)
(He also works on his face too.)
He's dressing up.
- He must be going somewhere. - He must be going somewhere.
Gosh, it's too hot.
Gosh, he's dressed to kill.
He must have an appointment in front of the station.
(Feeling shy)
(He heads to his appointment.)
Where will he be going?
- It's hard to predict. - Right.
- Hi. - What are you up to, Mom?
I'm getting ready to eat.
- I see. - You must be close to your mother.
I think we talk on the phone 4 to 5 times a week.
- Did you eat? - I had the skate.
Oh, really?
That's good to hear.
I made it with fresh skates.
Right. No wonder it was good.
"No wonder it was good?"
She likes hearing those things the most.
(The phone call of another good son pops up again.)
(It might be tough for you.)
(It is tough.)
(Giving himself all the credit in front of his mother)
(The mother-and-son relationships are quite different.)
They're very different.
What about Dad?
Dad is getting ready right now.
What about my older sister?
Your sister is lying around.
Stop sleeping now. You had enough sleep.
- She got a smack on her back. - Why scream like that?
I watched all of your YouTube videos.
I put up all the thumbs.
I really enjoyed them.
- She pressed the like button. - The like button.
She said she put up all the thumbs.
Okay. Bye.
Bye. I love you.
(Bye. I love you.)
My gosh. That's so sweet.
(He crosses the Han River...)
(and enters the expressway.)
I think he's going pretty far away.
Is he going to meet his parents?
He's in Gyeonggi Province.
(Past Seoul)
He's going far away. He's going all the way to Suwon?
I will be working on my commentating at the baseball stadium.
That is why I'm heading to Suwon.
(That is why I'm heading to Suwon.)
I'm almost there.
(This place...)
(is Suwon Wiz Park.)
It's Suwon Wiz Park.
(Professional baseball is at its peak right now.)
("Professional Baseball Reaches 9 Million Visitors in 528 Games")
("New Sales Record in 2025 with 224 Games Filled")
It was really hot that day.
Fans go to watch even when it's over 40°C.
No one can stop their passion.
(The lively sight of competition)
(It's a breathtaking sight.)
(He arrives at the baseball stadium.)
Will he practice on his own then?
- Won't there be someone to help? - Won't there be someone with him?
Gosh, it's so hot.
There must be someone there.
(He calls someone while taking in the sunlight fully.)
Where are you right now, sir?
Do you see the Samsung team buses?
Yes. I see three of them.
Around the team bus...
I think it's the one that helped Dae Ho.
- I'll see you there. - Okay. I'll be there.
(He feels the heat of the baseball stadium up close.)
(His heart starts beating at the thought of commentating.)
(Looking around)
Oh, right.
Sir!
You're here, Kang Yong.
- The angel? - It's him.
- It's Announcer Kim Na Jin. - Right.
- Dae Ho's savior. - The angel announcer.
(Dae Ho's savior who taught Dae Ho in Paris)
He's such a sweet guy.
(He also advises Kang Yong whenever he can.)
Right. I remember.
Senior Na Jin is a representative sportscaster of MBC.
(The all-round caster of all sports)
He can work with any sport.
The comments of sportscasters are really important too.
- Right. - Right.
When the Twins won the championship,
Na Jin made the fans emotional...
with his championship call.
What was it again?
(When the Twins won the championship in 2023)
The Twins won the championship in 29 years.
Right.
Who were you in fall of 1994?
And who are you now today?
("Korea Series Match 5 Championship Call Brings Tears")
("Fans Shed Tears After Hearing Commentator's Championship Call")
This is the live footage.
- Is there no script for that? - No.
- It's just written beforehand. - He prepared it beforehand.
- Right. - That comment is so impressive.
Recently, I was the sportscaster for College Basketball.
The Sangju competition.
(Kang Yong made his debut as a sportscaster.)
He watched the whole thing from start to finish...
and wrote down all of his feedback.
- Gosh. - What an angel.
- I got so surprised. - He's really an angel.
I really choked up after seeing that.
I'm his junior by many years,
and I was really moved that he wrote all those for me.
That's not an easy thing to do.
That's how much he loves his juniors...
and sincerely treats them.
He's like a role model to you, Kang Yong.
- That's right. - He's like that.
(And he admires him so much.)
We've only come here...
- for broadcasting, - Right.
So I couldn't teach you anything.
- Oh, right. - Yes.
It's better to just set a day aside...
and learn it at once.
- Thank you for coming. - Great work.
Great work.
(Super excited)
Let's say you're broadcasting the game for real.
Traffic was really heavy on the way.
How are you going to put it?
Oh, while mentioning the traffic?
You need to keep all these factors...
in your head.
- I can use them while commenting. - That's right.
That's a great tip.
That could build him a character.
You could explain the atmosphere...
before the game starts.
What did you see?
I was at a red light at the intersection,
the KT Wiz fans and the Samsung Lions fans...
kept crossing the road when it was two hours before the game.
- That's good. At the crosswalk? - So...
- Yes, at the crosswalk. - That's right.
Seeing the endless line of fans,
I thought their fight for the rankings would be endless too.
(Impressed)
That's a good one.
- That's good. - That was really nice.
- Seriously. - You're good.
(He thought of what to say while listening to his senior's advice.)
Since it's a fight...
- between 3rd and 5th places. - Good. You're a sportscaster.
Since it's a fight between 3rd and 5th places.
I wanted to use wordplay a little.
That was cool.
Everything is a source.
- Let's go up. - Okay.
- That's why you told me to take it. - These days...
(Following the veteran)
- Isn't that area for spectators? - The stadium that's open...
It's open and spacious.
It was my first time there.
(Opening the door without hesitation)
It's the broadcast control room.
The skybox.
You could wait here too.
This is the commentary booth.
- There's no AC in here. - We use...
- a fan here. - A fan? I see.
- It must be really hot in summer. - Is it because of the noise?
- Right. It's because of the noise. - To prevent any noise...
while commenting.
(Jaw-dropping)
(Impressed)
It's really close.
(The commentary booth's view is unobstructed.)
(The baseball field unfolds right in front.)
- You can see everything. - You can't help...
but get excited there.
It's like a VIP seat.
It's right at the center.
How fascinating.
The seat with the best view.
- And also... - Yes.
- That's amazing. - If you sit here...
(No matter how many times he looks, the view seems surreal.)
How did you feel when you entered the booth?
I was really excited.
I could see everything,
and I learned that they commented while watching everything from here.
I get to see a clip like this.
I only got to watch a clip where one drinks beer.
(Baseball games are all about beers.)
You're right.
Right.
- If you sit... - The view is amazing.
- It's like a view in a game. - Right. I'd love to go there.
Using this... Wait.
You can use it to rewatch.
- We are... - What is it?
Is someone here?
If you're in sports broadcasting,
- you ought to know him. - Gosh, you're flattering me.
- He's like... - Come on.
The textbook of broadcasting.
(A unique comment, "A three-strikeout while standing")
The man of that voice.
(Well-received by the baseball fans)
(Sportscaster Kim Soo Hwan)
- It's Director Kim Soo Hwan. - Goodness.
- Hello, I'm Ko Kang Yong. - Nice to meet you.
(Glancing)
Kang Yong admires you a lot.
- I really do. - Come on.
I've watched a lot of UFC games that you broadcasted.
- Really? - Yes.
- Nice to meet you. - I'm a really big fan.
You've got to believe it.
(Smiling right away upon seeing his favorite sportscaster)
He must've been a big fan.
- Right. - I was really happy.
It was really fascinating.
It was really fascinating to see him up close.
I'd only heard his voice,
but hearing his voice in person was really fascinating.
- You can't forget that. - You can't.
You can't.
The moment of seeing his star.
You do dubbing too.
- I do. - I've been watching it carefully.
- Really? - What did you think?
Please give an evaluation.
- I need to know, so... - I was worried at first.
(Nervous)
(Gulping)
- But I could see him grow. - "Grow."
- Really? - My juniors...
- are keeping you in check. - Really?
- Really? - That's for sure.
I thought they didn't know my existence.
- Of course we do. - They always watch you.
- Really? I'm really honored. - He does, at least.
- Say hello. - Hey.
- Hello. - What a coincidence.
- I'm Ko Kang Yong. - Nice to meet you.
Who is that?
- Say hello. - Hey.
- Hello. - What a coincidence.
- I'm Ko Kang Yong. - Nice to meet you.
Who is that?
This is a fan.
- Isn't that Jeon In Kwon? - Jeon In Kwon...
(He was famously known as Wild Horse.)
He's a legend.
The idol of LG Twins fans.
- He's the legend of LG Twins. - He's a legend.
("Wild Horse Lee Sang Hoon Experiences Baseball...")
- He was really good. - He's a legend.
("in Korea, America, and Japan for the First time as a Korean")
He's a commentator now.
It wasn't the day for Na Jin to commentate.
Soo Hwan did that day.
(Stunned)
It must've been a really meaningful time.
- An unforgettable moment. - I'll never forget it.
- Good luck. - Good luck with commentating.
- Keep up the good work. - Keep up the good work.
Shall we go to the broadcast van?
Come this way.
(Impressed)
Gosh, the broadcast van is really fascinating.
It's my first time going into one.
- I've only seen it. - You need to know...
what they do in the van.
You need to know what they're preparing...
and what they're focusing on,
so it'd be easier for you when you broadcast.
You must stop by the van before the game.
Bring drinks like this.
Tell them to keep up the good work and give it to them.
(Boosting the youngest's morale)
Goodness, seriously...
- He's a really cool senior. - Seriously...
You must go see him during Chuseok.
I really will.
Gosh, so that's how it looks.
- Here. - Hello.
(Entering the broadcast van, following Na Jin)
(With cutting-edge broadcasting equipment...)
- How fascinating. - That's amazing.
It was almost like the sub-control room.
It was really fascinating.
(The sub-control room that oversees "MBC News Today")
It looks exactly like the sub-control room.
Sir, is it okay to bother you?
Yes.
Hello, I'm...
- I'm MBC Announcer, Ko Kang Yong. - He's the new announcer, Kang Yong.
Nice to meet you.
- Na Jin got this drink. - He prepared...
- Gosh, he got you this. - Thank you.
He's the chief manager of broadcasting.
He controls everything...
from cameras to equipment. He's the chief manager.
So ask him whatever you want.
Can you teach him...
- how to control the cameras? - Basically...
We numbered every camera, as you can see.
- Are there 12 in total? - We are using...
thirteen cameras.
What I do is go to certain cameras...
and decide which screen to show, like Camera 7 or Camera 8.
But there's no such thing as a rehearsal in sports.
So you shift to another camera while watching the screens.
Then the completed scenes are transmitted.
When Dae Ho shot water,
- did you prepare in advance? - We have it here.
- Where? You prepared in advance... - That's right.
Shot water?
What is that?
Over there. He was on screen all of a sudden.
A scene like that.
Dae Ho was at the stadium the day before.
- I thought he was busy. - What is he doing?
- He's shooting water there? - What is he doing there?
He's become really free.
He's too free.
He danced with cheerleaders too.
Oh, my goodness!
(Sexy)
(Dancing in sync)
He's become a middle-aged man.
- He does whatever he wants now. - It's embarrassing for us.
My former senior.
Since he left.
He looks so happy.
Is there something...
you wished sportscasters did?
What are some of the virtues of a sportscaster?
Sports broadcast producers...
create scenes that sportscasters want.
On the other hand, we also want the sportscasters...
to lead the comment to certain ways.
When we create scenes with such intention,
they must be able to catch what we want.
(They must be able to catch the producer's intention.)
So the editing and comments need to go hand in hand.
- Yes. - You should pick up on things fast.
- That's right, to match the scenes. - You need to be sensible.
You can see this, right?
That's right.
"Even if you live separately, you're still family."
That kind of timing is also important.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you, sir.
(I'll keep that in mind.)
- Keep up the good work. - Yes, you too.
- Keep up the good work. - Thank you, sir.
Bye.
I secured an empty commentary booth.
Let's practice commentating...
while watching the game...
- and filling out record sheets. - Okay.
Na Jin secured a booth next to the commentary booth...
- of that day. - Just like actual broadcasting?
That's amazing. That's such a good experience.
(The two seniors are busy preparing for the broadcast.)
It feels different, right?
- It's really different. - Yes.
(Practicing like it's an actual broadcast)
It's really close.
- Did you bring record sheets? - Yes, I did.
- We need to take a look. - What are record sheets?
- Gosh. - What is that?
- Oh, it's from a previous game. - That's amazing.
For record sheets...
Write down the names of the players here.
- I differentiate them with colors. - I see.
Every sportscaster has a different way of writing.
He really is a veteran.
Gosh, that's impressive.
You need to bring out the things that you wrote down here.
(You can tell the charisma of the veteran from the sheet.)
Is it a record of players' participation...
- and their batting average? - Their records.
There's a separate record of that.
- What is this? - It's a record of the game.
If you look here, there's a list of hitters.
- And a list of innings. - Yes.
It's a record of whether there was a hit...
or a double in each inning.
- Or a 3-strikeout. - Or a 3-strikeout.
- He converted that into a symbol... - So it's easier to see.
And recorded it.
Today, we have Coach Park Jin Man.
I wrote down what he did and where,
and his coaching staff,
so it's easier to see.
Write down the coaching staff here.
You need to keep a record in your own style.
- I see. - Yes.
You need to memorize the information about the stadium.
- He's right. - This is so much fun.
What represents Suwon?
- Big galbi chicken. - The Hwaseong...
- Oh, it's the Hwaseong Fortress. - Yes, it's the Hwaseong Fortress.
He's right too.
- Such things... - Big galbi chicken is famous too.
Oh, it's the Hwaseong Fortress.
You need to know the history of that area too.
- You need to know a lot. - If you look here...
Add the Korea Meteorological Administration to shortcut.
To check the weather.
It includes the sunrise and sunset times.
- Okay. - Things like this.
You need to check the expected temperature.
Is it really possible to prepare all this?
You need to talk about such things too.
There are so many things to prepare.
That's right.
I watch baseball games a lot.
(A true baseball fan who always watches baseball games)
I'd hear the information that sportscasters share,
and I'd learn such information.
"Oh, that was why."
The sportscasters that share information...
- are really useful for the fans. - That's right.
There are no other sports games...
- that last this long. - That's right.
- Sportscasters need to speak a lot. - That's right.
There's nothing they can say if there are like ten foul balls.
- Then what should you do? - "What's wrong with him?"
You can't just say that.
- Right? It gets really boring. - That's right.
- Then what should you do? - You're right.
- You talk about such things. - You need to explain it.
- Yes, you need to explain. - Why the player hit a foul ball.
You need to be really creative.
(10 minutes before the game)
(The fans enter one by one.)
Gosh, this is like...
(Wiz versus Lions)
- It was packed. - In this weather?
Baseball stadiums are always packed.
(The broadcasting starts as well.)
(Super nervous)
(It begins now.)
A heat wave warning has been issued throughout the country.
Here, the Suwon KT Wiz Park is filled with even more heat...
- as the second game proceeds... - There's no script,
and he just says whatever...
- he thinks of. - There's no script at all.
Have you thought of what to say for the opening?
Yes, I prepared a simple one.
(The commentary he's making for the first time at the stadium)
KT Wiz that's aiming for third place...
and Samsung Lions aiming for fifth place...
are fighting against each other in the scorching heat of 35°C.
Yesterday, Son Dong Hyun appeared in the top of the 9th inning,
and he showed a magical three-strikeout,
leading KT Wiz to victory.
Will Samsung Lions be able...
to take victory and stop themselves...
- from three consecutive losses? - He's good.
Or will KT Wiz continue its winning streak for the fifth time...
and get a step closer to third place?
Let us find out together.
- Gosh, that was neat, indeed. - Was it okay?
The opening comment was amazing.
- Really? - Yes.
(Relieved)
I made use of 3rd and 5th place with 35°C.
That was nice.
- That was so forced. - Wait.
- That was related? - That was...
- I just found out. - I just found out.
- Wait. You used 3 and 5 like that? - Who would know?
Baseball fans know.
- Baseball fans... - You could've also said...
the fans came in groups of 3 and 5.
- I could've used that. - Yes, groups of 3 and 5.
If you keep sticking to such humor,
fans might look forward to it.
- "What will he say today?" - Right? That's right.
One of the sportscasters of the KBO League...
always reads a poem during the opening.
He became really famous for it.
- Just like that, if you have... - Like your own signature.
- Yes, like a signature comment. - That's right.
- That'd be nice. - It's like your character.
You need a character of your own.
(The game begins with Kang Yong's impressive opening.)
Great pitches by both teams' starting pitchers...
and the infielders' defense.
(Staring)
(Suddenly getting up)
- What could it be? - It smells amazing.
- That looks like chicken. - Chicken?
(For his senior who used his holiday to study with him)
- You need to eat well... - It's chicken.
To talk for like 3 to 4 hours.
Chickens at baseball stadiums are the best.
That's true.
It's my first time having chicken at a commentary booth.
- Even if we have chicken... - It looks so good.
You need to focus...
- on the game. - Yes.
All right?
- A fly out to center field. - A fly out to center field.
(His eyes focus on the game, just as his senior advised.)
(Shall I take a bite?)
(Screaming)
What's going on?
(The ball slipped between the 3rd baseman and the shortstop.)
- It's a hit. - It slipped in between.
- Kang Yong, this is important. - Yes.
What was that?
What was important?
A ball that slipped between the third baseman and the shortstop.
It wasn't just a hit. What do you call it?
What kind of hit was it?
- It looks like he was eating, - From the center?
- but he was watching everything. - Today...
It was the first hit for both teams.
You need to point that out.
- I see. - You should point out what it is.
(He writes it down on the sheet right away.)
It was thrown to the second baseman, Yang Do Geun.
Catching it lightly, it's a two-out.
The second baseman, Kim Seong Yoon catches it...
and throws it to the first base.
That's it.
That was good, but you said something wrong.
- What? - That was good, but...
- You said something wrong? - Just now.
Who was the second baseman?
Ryu Ji Hyeok.
The second baseman was...
- Yang Do Geun. I see. - Yang Do Geun.
- When the one on the outfield... - He said the wrong name?
Comes into the infield...
(I made a mistake on the name.)
I get that you didn't have time,
but you can't make a mistake on their names.
- You'll be in big trouble. - This is not right.
You can never make a mistake on this.
You can't.
A different player was in the position of the player...
who played the day before.
- So I thought he'd be there. - No.
- So I was... - You can't do that.
Quite careless when I made that comment.
The batter with 2 outs and a runner on the 1st and 2nd base.
On the 2nd base is Yang Do Geun, and on the 1st base...
(Oh, dear...)
On the 2nd base is Lee Jae Hyeon, and on the 1st base is Yang Do Geun.
It's their first crisis and...
(His thoughts are all jumbled as he's focusing on the names.)
(Sighing)
It's his crisis!
What should I call it? A crisis and a chance at the same time?
- What's that? - What should I call it?
Is it a foreign movie dubbing?
Are you dubbing or something?
- "My teacher told me." - What should I call it?
"James told me."
How can a sportscaster go, "What should I call it?"
- "What should I call it?" - "What should I call it?"
It gets you immersed, though.
- You're right. - You're right.
It really is like a dubbing for an American movie.
That's incredible.
It's a flyball for Jurado.
Even I'm burning inside.
- You missed it, right? - Yes, I did.
(He even makes a mistake recording while focusing on the names.)
You need to write it down real-time.
You must be really busy.
- He steps out after... - Gosh, it's really hard.
Write it down right away. See if you made any mistakes.
Remember where all the defenders are.
You must practice a lot.
I can't seem to go on.
It's only natural.
Seriously.
I felt lost.
There were so many things to keep an eye on.
I had to check the scoreboard too.
That's right.
And I had to watch the screens in front of me.
- I had to look at the sheets too. - Memorizing names is...
You can't make a mistake on the names.
And I had to think of what to say too.
There were so many things to do.
I didn't know what to sort out first...
and what to say first.
I was really lost.
(He can't even eat the chicken.)
(His hand is busy, and so are his eyes.)
You need to keep mentioning their names.
- Gosh, it's hard. - That must be really hard.
You need to like baseball...
to be able to keep up.
It's a ground ball. The third baseman advances,
but Hur Kyoung Min catches the difficult ball...
and throws it to the first base. He's out.
- That was good. - Here,
you should raise your energy level up.
He caught it. It was a difficult ground ball.
Hur Kyoung Min! My gosh.
Without having to use descriptive words,
you need to leave an impact. You don't have to elaborate.
The difficult ground ball on the third base. Hur Kyoung Min!
Hur Kyoung Min is great, indeed!
- That was a perfect defense. - I see.
- He didn't say much. - Right.
- You can just keep it simple. - Okay.
His season batting average is 0.265.
He's proving himself as the ace of starting players.
Using the quick feet of a center fielder,
he treated it well. That's two outs.
Sportscaster Ko Kang Yong knows what to point out.
He's moved.
I feel more relaxed now.
Swing and miss! Three-strikeout.
So Hyeong Jun escapes a crisis.
Gosh, that's nice.
(Feeling proud of himself)
- He compliments a lot. - From here,
you don't need to say much.
Discuss whether they'll be able to score or not.
(It's 0 to 0 even in the 7th inning.)
(Fans from both teams are tense.)
KT Wiz positions in for defense.
It's nerve-racking.
All the runners are in scoring positions.
One out and runners on third and second.
KT Wiz isn't willing to give any score,
based on their defense.
We can see such determination.
That they will never concede.
(And...)
That's a big hit.
- He hit it. - They made it.
(It's their first score of the day.)
He hit the fifth pitch, and the ball goes to the center.
The runner on the third base...
and the runner on the second base score as well.
The batter is taken out on the second base.
Samsung Lions scores first.
(Glancing)
(Staring at the scoreboard)
Samsung Lions leads with a score of 2 to 0.
(Thumbs up)
Good.
Well done.
- Write down the scores as well. - Yes. Right.
There. You have so many things to do.
He'll catch up really soon since he has a nice tone.
His tone is very catchy.
The Samsung Lions fans are buzzing.
- No one is sitting... - It's getting heated.
- except for KT Wiz fans. - The momentum shifted.
You're right.
- They finally scored. - Yes.
So it's better to shout.
- I see. - Yes.
You can shout all you want.
It's going high.
It's going behind the center fielder.
It went past the fence.
Kim Young Woong puts the game out.
- That's great. - It's...
- a three-run home run. - How can he say that right away?
It's 9 to 0. Samsung Lions is leading.
(Thanks to Na Jin's coaching, he smoothly says his comments.)
He hit it.
(They got up from their seats as things got heated.)
(He comments on top of his lungs while standing.)
It goes beyond the second baseman.
(Kang Yong becomes more and more confident.)
Even the second baseman scores.
I've watched sports games in person since 2003.
I watched Jeonju KCC's basketball game in Jeonju Gymnasium.
I was a little boy then.
I didn't go to cram school to watch basketball games.
I couldn't believe it.
Actually, I have to go to work really early in the morning.
I studied sports broadcasting until late in the evening,
and I even went to the stadium.
Still, it's fine for me.
Because I'm doing what I like,
I'm really happy.
The second hitter hits it.
(He happily spent his holiday by working.)
(I'm Happy Because I Do What I Love)
(Next story)
(Today, )
(I'm going back...)
(to my old self.)
I got a scuba diving certification.
(Recalling the old days when he was one with water)
(He returns to the sea.)
It's both scary and nerve-racking.
(He'd freely float around.)
(Greeting the friends from the same hometown)
(Abalone)
I felt like I became a dugong.
(The Return of Prince Dugong)
(I believe there are past lives.)
(Isn't it amazing that you're alive right now?)
(Why am I alive now, of all times?)
(What I want to say...)
(Maybe...)
(I was a dinosaur.)
(Maybe dinosaur genes have been passed down.)
(What's the truth?)
(Curious)
(Docent)
(Teach me more about dinosaurs, Mr. Docent.)
(Even a giant ammonite)
(Oh, they eat ammonites.)
(Step by step)
(He walks into the world of dinosaurs.)
(Serious)
(Where I'm living...)
Dinosaurs.
(Summoning dinosaurs)
(The Jurassic Park opens.)
(The Birth of Juranosaurus)